http://www.candlewic.com/service/about-candlewic/privacy-and-security/page.aspx?id=1781

Privacy and Security | Candlewic
HomeNewSaleMy AccountMy Cart
Professional Candle Making Supplies Since 1972
Candle MakingCandle WaxCandlewic Custom BlendsParaffin WaxSoy Candle WaxBeeswaxBeeswax SheetsPalm Candle WaxNatural Candle WaxesGranulated Candle WaxCandle Wax AdditivesGel Wax & InsertsCanning WaxSpa WaxWicksCustom Wick BuilderWooden WicksSpools of WickingStandard Candle Wick AssembliesWick Tabs / Sustainer Candle BasesWick PinsMoldsAccessories for MoldsAluminum MoldsBeeswaxDesigner Shaped PlasticFloating Candle MoldsClam Shell MoldsPlastic MoldsTapersTea-LightVotiveCandle DyeColor BlocksDiamond Color ChipsLiquid DyesPigment DyesContainersAll GlasswareCandle JarsLibbey Glass JarsMason JarsApothecary JarsHex JarsTureen JarsCandle TinsBoxes & LabelsEquipmentPouring PotsBars, Bowties & Glue DotsWax Melters & HeatersRubber PlugsTaper Candle ToolsThermometersWholesale CandlesCandle Making Kits - Great for beginners!Soap MakingBasesMelt & Pour BasesBath & Body BasesOils & FragrancesEssential OilsSingle Essential OilsFractionated Coconut OilSoap Friendly ScentsMoldsRubber MoldsTray MoldsMetal Loaf MoldsDyesDyes for Soap MakingIngredientsPlant OilsButtersOther Natural IngredientsFragrances By TypeUltimate & BoldClassic & StandardDesigner & BrandSoap FriendlyFeaturedNewBest SellersOn SaleAromasFood & DrinkFreshEarthyFloralSeasonsSpringSummerFallWinterEssential OilsAromatherapySingle Essential OilsFractionated Coconut OilCombo PacksReed DiffusersReedsDiffuser BasesReed Diffuser OilsCITRUSFLORALFRESHFRUITYGOURMETView All 300+ Candle & Soap Fragrances!EducationHow ToWhat You'll NeedCandle Making Instructions Simple Container CandlePillar CandlesSoy Wax CandlesNatural CandlesGel CandlesBeeswax CandlesVotive CandlesChoosing Candle WaxChandler's Guide for BeginnersVideosProduction Facility VideosCandle Wick VideosCandle Wax VideosHow to VideosOther Product VideosTips & TechniquesTipsTechniquesTechniques for Visual EffectsCandle Making Test SheetProjectsCandle ContainersDecorative Candle ProjectsKids Candle ProjectsSummer Candle ProjectsCandle Projects & CraftsFall Candle ProjectBusiness TipsBusiness BasicsPricing TipsProduct Improvement Marketing TipsCandle Making Business GuidesFAQsFrequently Asked QuestionsQuestions About SuppliesSoap MakingAsk a QuestionShopping HelpWaxWicks & ColorGreen Candlemaking Candlewic's Newsletter - The En-Light-ener - Back IssuesServiceAbout CandlewicHistory of CandlewicAffiliate ProgramLocation & DirectionsPrivacy and SecurityThe History of Candles and CandlemakingCustom Services Custom Wick AssembliesCustom Granulated WaxCustom Wax Processing & PackagingCustom Liquid FillingOrdering About My Order CatalogReturns Terms & Conditions ShippingTrack My OrderShipping MethodsInternational OrdersCustomer SupportSpeak with a Representative Website Problems Contact UsReturns Report a ProblemAsk a QuestionSafety Safety TipsCandle Making BasicsCandle Making Instructions Join our email list and receive $10 off a $50 or more purchaseSIGN ME UP!
HomeServiceAbout CandlewicPrivacy and Security
About CandlewicHistory of CandlewicAffiliate ProgramLocation/DirectionsPrivacy and SecurityThe History of Candles and Candlemaking
Privacy and Security
Share:
Information Collection and Use
Candlewic is the sole owner of the information collected on this site (www.candlewic.com). We will not sell, share, or rent this information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement. Candlewic collects information from our users at several different points on our website.
Registration. In order to use certain features of this website, a user must first complete the registration form. During registration a user is required to give their contact information (such as name and email address). This information is used to contact the user about the services on our site for which they have expressed interest. It is optional for the user to provide demographic information (such as income level and gender), but encouraged so we can provide a more personalized experience on our site.Order. We request information from the user on our order form. Here a user must provide contact information (like name and shipping address) and financial information (like credit card number, expiration date). This information is used for billing purposes and to fill customer's orders. If we have trouble processing an order, this contact information is used to get in touch with the user.Cookies. A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's hard drive containing information about the user. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information while on our site. Once the user closes their browser, most cookies simply terminate. For instance, by setting a cookie on our site, the user would not have to log in a password more than once, thereby saving time while on our site. If a user rejects the cookie, they may still use our site. The only drawback to this is that the user will be limited in some areas of our site. Cookies can also enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our site.Log Files. We use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the site, track user's movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information.Sharing. We will share aggregated demographic information with our partners and advertisers. This is not linked to any personal information that can identify any individual person. We use an outside shipping company to ship orders, and a credit card processing company to bill users for goods ordered on our site. These companies do not retain, share, store or use personally identifiable information for any secondary purposes. We may, in some cases, partner with another party to provide specific services. When the user signs up for these services, we will share names, or other contact information that is necessary for the third party to provide these services. These parties are not allowed to use personally identifiable information except for the purpose of providing these services.Links. This web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that Candlewic is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this web site.Newsletter. If a user wishes to subscribe to one of our newsletters, we ask for contact information such as name and email address.Surveys & Contests. From time-to-time our site requests information from users via surveys or contests. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and the user therefore has a choice whether or not to disclose this information. Information requested may include contact information (such as name and shipping address), and demographic information (such as zip code, age level). Contact information will be used to notify the winners and award prizes. Survey information will be used for purposes of monitoring or improving the use and satisfaction of this site.Security. This website takes every precaution to protect our users' information. When users submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and off-line.When our registration/order form asks users to enter sensitive information (such as credit card number), that information is encrypted and is protected with the best encryption software in the industry--SSL. While on a secure page, such as our order form, the lock icon on the bottom of Web browsers such as Netscape Navigator and Microsoft Internet Explorer becomes locked, as opposed to un-locked, or open, when you are just 'surfing'.While we use SSL encryption to protect sensitive information online, we also do everything in our power to protect user-information off-line. All of our users' information, not just the sensitive information mentioned above, is restricted in our offices. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, our billing clerk or a customer service representative) are granted access to personally identifiable information. Furthermore, ALL employees are kept up-to-date on our security and privacy practices. At various times throughout the year, as well as any time new policies are added, our employees are notified and/or reminded about the importance we place on privacy, and what they can do to ensure our customers' information is protected. Finally, the servers that we store personally identifiable information on are kept in a secure environment, in a locked room.If you have any questions about the security at our website, you can send an email to webmaster@mojoactive.com.Supplementation of Information. In order for this website to enhance its ability to tailor the site to an individual's preference, we may choose to combine information about the purchasing habits of users with similar information from other companies to create a personalized user profile.Special Offers. We send all customers a thank you email to confirm their orders. Established customers will occasionally receive information on products, services, special deals, and a newsletter. Out of respect for the privacy of our users we present the option to not receive these types of communications. Please see "Choice and Opt-Out" below.Site and Service Updates. We also send the user site and service announcement updates. Members are not able to un-subscribe from service announcements, which contain important information about the service. We communicate with the user to provide requested services and in regards to issues relating to their account via email or phone.Correction/Updating Personal Information. If a user's personally identifiable information changes (such as your zip code), or if a user no longer desires our service, we will endeavor to provide a way to correct, update or remove that user's personal data provided to us. This can usually be done by emailing our Customer Service Department.Choice/Opt-out. Our users are given the opportunity to 'opt-out' of having their information used for purposes not directly related to our site at the point where we ask for the information. For example, our order form has an 'opt-out' mechanism so users who buy a product from us, but don't want any marketing material, can keep their email address off of our lists. Users who no longer wish to receive our newsletter or promotional materials from our partners may opt-out of receiving these communications by following the directions supplied in each mailing. Users of our site are always notified when their information is being collected by any outside parties. We do this so our users can make an informed choice as to whether they should proceed with services that require an outside party, or not.Notification of Changes. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on our site so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under circumstances, if any, we disclose it. If at any point we decide to use personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will notify users by way of an email. Users will have a choice as to whether or not we use their information in this different manner. We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected.
SIGN UP FOR OUR NEWSLETTER AND RECEIVE
A FREE CANDLE MAKING eBOOK
Receive emails with the latest trends, projects, and ideas.
Join our mailing list & get a free candle crafts eBook (a $5 value).
View Candle Making Newsletter Back Issues
Supplies the candle and soap making industries with kits, molds, waxes, bases, and other accessories.
$75 purchase requiredClick the image above to view promo code.
Not responsible for typographical errors. Prices subject to change without notice.
For more on candle making check out the Candle Making Links page.
Website by MoJo Active, Inc.
